proxyway.com 2010-05-10

# Privacy Policy

|   
---  
---  
|  |   
---  
| 

---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
| 

---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|  |   
---  
**Monday, May 10, 2010**  
|  |  |  |   
---|---|---  
PROXIES MAIN QUESTIONS  
|  |  \- [What is a proxy server?](http://www.proxyway.com/what_is_a_proxy_server.html)  
\- [Why use proxies](http://www.proxyway.com/why_use_proxies.html)  
\- [How to use proxies](http://www.proxyway.com/how_to_use_proxies.html)  
\- [Types of proxies](http://www.proxyway.com/types_of_proxies.html)  
\- [HTTP proxies](http://www.proxyway.com/HTTP_proxies.html)  
\- [HTTPS proxy](http://www.proxyway.com/HTTPS_proxy.html)  
\- [SOCKS proxy](http://www.proxyway.com/SOCKS_proxy.html)  
\- [How to check proxy](http://www.proxyway.com/check_proxy.html)  
\- [How to find proxy list](http://www.proxyway.com/find_proxy_list.html)  
\- [How to change proxy](http://www.proxyway.com/change_proxy_settings.html)  
\- [Configure proxy settings](http://www.proxyway.com/configure_proxy_settings.html)  
\- [What is proxy chaining?](http://www.proxyway.com/what_is_proxy_chaining.html)  
\- [What is a web proxy?](http://www.proxyway.com/web_proxy.html)  
|   
---|---|---  
IP ADDRESS QUESTIONS  
|  |  \- [How to find IP address](http://www.proxyway.com/how_to_find_IP_address.html)  
\- [What is my IP address?](http://www.proxyway.com/what_is_my_IP_address.html)  
\- [Find IP location](http://www.proxyway.com/find_IP_location.html)  
\- [How to change IP address](http://www.proxyway.com/how_to_change_IP_address.html)  
|   
---|---|---  
BROWSING QUESTIONS  
|  |  \- [What is an HTTP header?](http://www.proxyway.com/what_is_http_header.html)  
\- [User-Agent header](http://www.proxyway.com/user_agent_header.html)  
\- [HTTP Referrer](http://www.proxyway.com/http_referrer.html)  
|   
---|---|---  
FREE PROXY LISTS  
|  |  How to find free proxy lists:  
[Proxy lists](http://www.bestproxylists.com/) from different countries  
|   
---|---|---  
PROXY TIPS  
|  |  Proxy software 'must have' features:  
\- [Proxy List Filter](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-list-filter.html) that helps you easily select proxies according to their [anonymity](http://www.proxyway.com/www/check-proxy-anonymity.html), proxy speed, protocol type, country, IP and port number  
\- [Proxy changer option](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-changer.html)  
\- [Proxy checker](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-checker.html) ([proxy anonymity checker](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-anonymity-checker.html) with detecting proxy location)  
\- Ability to easily create [proxy chains](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-chain-software.html)  
\- Proxy finder  
\- Ability to import and export proxies in different formats  
|   
---|---|---  
|  |  What is Proxy Finder?  
Proxy Finder searches for HTTP proxy lists, HTTPS proxy lists and SOCKS (SOCKS4, SOCKS4A, SOCKS5, SOCKS5 with Authentication) proxies lists on the Internet. You should specify proxy web site URL(s) where proxy lists are located and Proxy Finder will automatically find proxy servers information. Then proxy/proxies are added to the program proxy list. Also some proxy finders can check added proxies on fly or by your request. Usually proxies can be checked for proxy state, proxy speed, proxy location and proxy anonymity.  
Most proxy finder tools allow you to:  
\- Scan proxy web sites and extract HTTP proxy lists, HTTPS proxy list and SOCKS proxies list  
\- Recognize different proxy list formats  
\- Import/export proxy lists  
\- Search proxies from certain countries  
\- Extract proxies from different proxy lists simultaneously  
\- Automatically search for proxies using scheduler  
|   
---|---|---  
QUICK LINKS  
|  |  \- [Anonymous web surfing](http://www.proxyway.com/www/anonymous-web-surfing-d.html)  
\- [Search proxies](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-proxy-tool/proxy-search-proxies.html)  
\- [MySpace proxy servers](http://www.proxyway.com/www/myspace-proxy-servers.html)  
\- [MySpace proxy sites](http://www.proxyway.com/www/myspace-proxy-sites.html)  
\- [Facebook bypass list](http://www.proxyway.com/www/facebook-bypass.html)  
\- [YouTube unblocker](http://www.proxyway.com/www/youtube-unblocker.html)  
\- [Unblock Facebook at school](http://www.proxyway.com/www/unblock-facebook-at-school.html)  
\- [Erase web history](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-internet-eraser/web-eraser.html)  
\- [Proxy finder]()  
\- [New Facebook proxy](http://www.proxyway.com/www/new-facebook-proxy.html)  
\- [Delete computer cookies](http://www.proxyway.com/www/delete-computer-cookies.html)  
\- [Free proxy software](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-proxy-software/free-proxy-server-software-new.html)  
\- [Cache cleaner](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-internet-cleaner/cache-cleaner.html)  
\- [Free proxy tools](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-proxy-tool/free-proxy-server-tools.html)  
\- [Proxy server software](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-proxy-software/proxy-server-software-new.html)  
\- [Internet history cleaner](http://www.proxyway.com/www/internet-cleaner.html)  
\- [Free proxy surfing software](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-proxy-surfing-software.html)  
\- [How to bypass school firewall](http://www.proxyway.com/www/bypass-school-firewall.html)  
\- [Tracks eraser](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-internet-eraser/track-eraser.html)  
\- [Bebo unblock](http://www.proxyway.com/www/bebo-unblock.html)  
\- [Proxy unblock](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-unblock.html)  
\- [Internet tracks eraser software](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-internet-eraser/internet-eraser-software.html)  
\- [Anonymous proxy tool](http://www.proxyway.com/www/anonymous-proxy-tool/anonymous-proxy-tool.html)  
\- [Unblock YouTube](http://www.proxyway.com/www/unblock-youtube.html)  
\- [Internet history cleaner](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-internet-cleaner/free-internet-history-cleaner.html)  
\- [Unblock proxies](http://www.proxyway.com/www/unblock-proxies.html)  
\- [How to bypass firewall](http://www.proxyway.com/www/bypass-firewall.html)  
\- [Delete temporary internet files](http://www.proxyway.com/www/delete-temporary-internet-files.html)  
\- [Anonymous proxy surfing](http://www.proxyway.com/www/anonymous%20proxy%20surfing.html)  
\- [History eraser](http://www.proxyway.com/www/erase-history-eraser.html)  
\- [MySpace unblock](http://www.proxyway.com/www/myspace-unblock.html)  
\- [MySpace unblocker](http://www.proxyway.com/www/myspace-unblocker.html)  
\- [Free history eraser](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-internet-eraser/free-history-eraser.html)  
\- [Hide my IP address](http://www.proxyway.com/www/hide-my-IP/hide-my-IP.html)  
\- [Block internet cookies](http://www.proxyway.com/www/block-internet-cookies-computer.html)  
\- [Anonymous web browsing](http://www.proxyway.com/www/anonymous-web-browsing/anonymous-web-browsing.html)  
\- [Freeware download](http://www.freewaredownload.org/)  
\- [Hide ip address free](http://www.proxyway.com/www/hiding-ip-address-free/hide-ip-address-tool.html)  
\- [How to clear history](http://www.clearallhistory.com/)  
\- [Anonymous proxy software](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-proxy-software/anonymous-proxy-software.html)  
\- [Erase history](http://www.erase-history.net/)  
\- [How to delete cookies](http://www.deletecookiesnow.com/)  
\- [Delete history](http://www.deletehistoryfree.com/)  
\- [Web proxy list](http://www.freewebproxylist.com/)  
\- [How to bypass Internet filter](http://www.proxyway.com/www/bypass-internet-filter.html)  
\- [Bypass proxy solution](http://www.proxyway.com/www/bypass-proxy.html)  
\- [Bypass school filter](http://www.proxyway.com/www/bypass-school-filter.html)  
\- [Bypass web filter software](http://www.proxyway.com/www/bypass-web-filter.html)  
\- [Free MySpace proxy list](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-myspace-proxy.html)  
\- [IP tests and privacy tips](http://www.2privacy.com/)  
\- [Clear cache](http://www.clear-cache-cleaner.com/)  
\- [YouTube proxy servers](http://www.proxyway.com/www/youtube-proxy-servers.html)  
\- [YouTube proxy sites](http://www.proxyway.com/www/youtube-proxy-sites.html)  
\- [Internet history eraser](http://www.freeinternethistoryeraser.com/)  
\- [Email privacy](http://www.emailprivacy.info/)  
\- [Clear history](http://www.clear-history.org/)  
\- [How to get on MySpace at school](http://www.proxyway.com/www/get-on-myspace-at-school.html)  
\- [MySpace bypass list](http://www.proxyway.com/www/myspace-bypass.html)  
\- [MySpace proxies](http://www.proxyway.com/www/myspace-proxies.html)  
\- [MySpace proxy sites](http://www.proxyway.com/www/myspace-proxy.html)  
\- [Proxies to unblock Bebo](http://www.proxyway.com/www/bebo-proxies.html)  
\- [Bebo proxy list](http://www.proxyway.com/www/bebo-proxy-list.html)  
\- [Unblock Bebo](http://www.proxyway.com/www/unblock-bebo.html)  
\- [Erase history](http://www.eraseallhistory.com/)  
\- [MySpace proxy for school](http://www.proxyway.com/www/myspace-proxy-for-school.html)  
\- [MySpace proxy list](http://www.proxyway.com/www/myspace-proxy-list.html)  
\- [Stumble Upon](http://www.stumbleupon.com/)  
\- [International alliance](http://www.intl-alliance.com/)  
\- [Delete Files](http://www.deletefilespermanently.com/)  
\- [Proxy bypass filter](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-bypass-filter.html)  
\- [Proxy for MySpace](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-for-myspace.html)  
\- [Unblock MySpace at school](http://www.proxyway.com/www/unblock-myspace-at-school.html)  
\- [Proxy for MySpace](http://www.proxyway.com/www/unblock-myspace-proxy-site.html)  
\- [MySpace bypasser](http://www.proxyway.com/www/myspace-bypasser.html)  
\- [Clean history](http://www.cleanhistory.org/)  
\- [Unblock MySpace](http://www.proxyway.com/www/unblock-myspace.html)  
\- [How to get around firewall](http://www.proxyway.com/www/how-to-get-around-firewall.html)  
\- [How to bypass proxy server](http://www.proxyway.com/www/bypass-proxy-server.html)  
\- [Facebook proxies](http://www.proxyway.com/www/facebook-proxies.html)  
\- [Facebook proxy for school](http://www.proxyway.com/www/facebook-proxy-for-school.html)  
\- [Unlock YouTube tips](http://www.proxyway.com/www/unlock-youtube.html)  
\- [Facebook unblocker](http://www.proxyway.com/www/facebook-unblocker.html)  
\- [YouTube unblock](http://www.proxyway.com/www/youtube-unblock.html)  
\- [Proxy for Facebook](http://www.proxyway.com/www/unblock-facebook-proxy-site.html)  
|   
---|---|---  
  
|   
---  
|  **Privacy Policy**  
  
---  
  
By using this site, you accept all the terms and conditions of the ProxyWay.com Privacy Policy. The purpose of ProxyWay.com Privacy Policy is to inform you what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit ProxyWay.com and how we may use it, whether we may disclose gathered information to anyone, and your ability to change the information. This privacy practice applies only to ProxyWay.com, and not to other web sites to which we may link. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the site.  
ProxyWay.com respects your desire for privacy and ensures that your personal information submitted to ProxyWay.com is handled in a safe and responsible manner.  
**Information Collection and Use**  
ProxyWay.com does not collect any personal information about you except when you specifically provide it to us. Personal information provided by our customers is used to provide updated information on our products, help us process payment and send activation information to customers. Personal information collected on this site will not be shared with our partners or third parties and will be used for administrative and identification purposes only.  
We may use the information we gather to understand our users base more to improve the quality of our services; customize the advertising and content you see; send you information you agreed to receive about specials and new products and services, which you might be interested; perform your requests for certain products and services.  
We automatically gather and record usage information such as browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. This data is used to estimate the total number of users visiting ProxyWay.com from specific countries or regions of the world.  
ProxyWay.com uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  
**Cookies**  
Upon your first visit ProxyWay.com, ProxyWay.com sends a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a piece of data which often includes an unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers, stored on your computer and identifies you as a unique user.  
ProxyWay.com uses cookies and tracking technologies to estimate and report our total audience size and traffic; accumulate and report aggregated statistical information about ProxyWay.com site and advertisement usage; keep count of return visits to our site, determine our users interests and keep track of preferences you specify while you are using ProxyWay.com.  
Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, refuse all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit ProxyWay.com, however, if you refuse all cookies, some parts of the ProxyWay.com may not function properly.  
ProxyWay.com cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other information to tell us who you are. We also may provide aggregated statistical information, but never information which could identify you personally, to our partners about how our visitors, use ProxyWay.com, so they too can understand how much people use their areas and our site.  
ProxyWay.com will not disclose its cookies to third parties except as required by a valid legal process.  
**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
ProxyWay.com may share aggregated statistical information about our users with advertisers, business partners, and other third parties. We do not share personal information that you may give us to any third-parties. However, ProxyWay.com may share personal identifiable information about you to other companies or people to provide the service you have requested.  
Your information may be disclosed if we have a good faith belief that we are required to do so by law or legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of ProxyWay.com.  
If, at any time, ProxyWay.com is going to use your personal identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify you via email. You will have a choice if we may use your information in this different manner or not.  
WARNING: ProxyWay.com reserves the right to report any unauthorized or fraudulent credit card purchases to collection agents, reporting agencies and law enforcement authorities for investigation, recovery of economic damages, and/or criminal prosecution. Users of unauthorized or fraudulent credit cards hereby consent to ProxyWay.com's disclosure of such user's identity, subscriber information, and scope and content of Internet use to any such third parties. Furthermore, the users of unauthorized or fraudulent credit cards hereby acknowledge and agree that ProxyWay.com will not be responsible for, and is hereby released from, all consequences arising out of further disclosure of such user's information following ProxyWay.com's initial release of such data to any collection agent, reporting agency or law enforcement authority.  
**Links to other sites**  
ProxyWay.com provides links to third-party sites, which are not under the control of ProxyWay.com. ProxyWay.com is not responsible for the content and privacy policy on third-party sites.  
**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
ProxyWay.com Privacy Policy may be changed from time to time. Please review the Privacy Policy page periodically for any changes at: http://www.ProxyWay.com/www/info/proxyway-privacy.html.  
  
|   
---  
|   
  
---  
|  |  |   
---|---|---  

Do you want to know how private you are while internet surfing?  
[Check your IP address](http://www.proxyway.com/www/check-ip-address.html), [IP location](http://www.proxyway.com/www/check-ip-location.html), Internet privacy and your [anonymity](http://www.proxyway.com/anonymity-test.html) |   
---|---|---  

|  |  [Proxy Checker](http://www.proxyway.com/www/online-proxy-checker.html) \- automatically parses proxy lists and generates detailed information about proxy server response time, proxy location, proxy type, [proxy anonymity](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-anonymity-test.html) and functionality. So you can easily choose the proxy/proxies you want.  
Most [Proxy Checkers](http://www.proxyway.com/www/ip-proxy-checker.html) allows you to:  
\- Check proxies simultaneously  
\- [Check HTTP proxy lists](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-checker-software.html), HTTPS proxy list, SOCKS4, SOCKS5 proxy server lists  
\- Supports multithreading to check proxy list faster  
\- Check [proxy](http://www.proxyway.com/www/downloads/) server speed  
\- [Check proxy](http://www.proxyway.com/www/how-to-check-proxy.html) anonymity (anonymous proxy, high anonymous proxy, transparent proxy)  
\- [Check proxy](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-checker-tool.html) server location  
\- Check proxies functionality  
\- Import and export proxy list |   
---|---|---  
  
TOP LINKS   
  
|  |  \- [Privoxy](http://www.privoxy.org/)  
\- [Proxy Lists and Proxy Tools](http://tools.rosinstrument.com/)  
\- [Secret IP](http://www.secretip.com/)  
\- [Maxthon](http://www.maxthon.com/)  
\- [International Alliance Privacy Services](http://www.intl-alliance.com/)  
\- [Free IP Proxy Changer](http://members.home.nl/wantos/)  
\- [Anonymy Web](http://anonymy-web.fr/)  
\- [Email Privacy](http://emailprivacy.info/)  
\- [xRoxy](http://xroxy.com/) |   
---|---|---  

|  |  [Every time you surf the web you are subject to different ](http://www.proxyway.com/www/clear-history.html)[Internet risks](http://www.proxyway.com/www/anonymous-internet-browsing.html) including hackers, identity thieves, spammers and other people who want to get access to your computer and monitor your [activities](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-server-anonymous-public-faq.html)

Do you know ...  
Your computer tracks everything you are doing while using the computer or surfing the Internet  
... Your online and offline activities are not private as surfing tracks, cache, downloaded files and some identifying data is stored on your computer.  
... Some tracks of computer and Internet activity can't be removed manually without special tracks eraser software.  
If you don't protect your information, your surfing habits and private information could be tracked and stolen. You may compromise your privacy and even become a victim of identify theft.  
[Privacy eraser](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-internet-eraser/privacy-eraser.html) software will keep your private information by [deleting history](http://www.proxyway.com/www/delete-internet-history.html) that is collected on your computer while surf the web: a history of the web sites you have visited, images and movies you have seen, files you downloaded, documents and files you have just opened, cookies that web sites store on your computer, emails, passwords and logins you use to access various accounts over the web, your credit card number and other confidential information.

|   
---|---|---  
  
QUICK LINKS   
  
|  |  \- [Anonymous surfing](http://www.proxyway.com/www/anonymous-surfing-how.html)  
\- [Internet anonymous proxy surf](http://www.proxyway.com/www/anonymous-proxy-surf-internet.html)  
\- [Web anonymous surfing](http://www.proxyway.com/www/anonymous-proxy-surfing-web.html)  
\- [Change ip address free](http://www.proxyway.com/www/changing-ip-address-free/change-ip-address-software.html)  
\- [YouTube proxy list](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-youtube-proxy.html)  
\- [Unlock MySpace tips](http://www.proxyway.com/www/unlock-myspace.html)  
\- [Free Facebook proxy list](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-facebook-proxy.html)  
\- [How to get on Facebook at school](http://www.proxyway.com/www/get-on-facebook-at-school.html)  
\- [Facebook proxy sites](http://www.proxyway.com/www/facebook-proxy-sites.html)  
\- [Facebook unblock](http://www.proxyway.com/www/facebook-unblock.html)  
\- [Change IP Address](http://www.changeipaddress.org/)  
\- [Shredd files](http://www.fileshredderpro.com/)  
\- [Proxy for Facebook](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-for-facebook.html)  
\- [YouTube proxy list](http://www.proxyway.com/www/youtube-proxy-list.html)  
\- [Free Proxy Tools](http://www.proxyway.com/www/downloads.html) \- [Change ip address software]()  
\- [Free anonymous proxy lists](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-proxy-lists/free-anonymous-proxy-server-lists.html)   
\- [Free proxy sites](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-proxy-sites/proxy-sites-list.html)  
\- [Top Shareware](http://www.topshareware.com/)  
\- [Free proxy server list](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-proxy-server-list.html)  
\- [Proxy sites list](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-sites-list.html)  
\- [Unblocked proxy](http://www.proxyway.com/www/unblocked-proxy.html)  
\- [Bebo proxy sites](http://www.proxyway.com/www/bebo-proxy-sites.html)  
\- [YouTube proxy list](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-youtube.html)  
\- [History cleaner](http://www.historycleaner.net/)  
\- [Free web proxies](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-web-proxies.html)  
\- [Free proxies sites](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-proxies-sites.html)  
\- [Free web proxy](http://www.proxyway.com/www/web-proxy/free-web-proxy-server.html)  
\- [Why to surf anonymously](http://www.proxyway.com/www/surf-anonymous-why.html)  
\- [Clear History](http://www.clearallhistory.com/)  
\- [Clear search history](http://www.clearallhistory.com/clear-search-history.html)  
\- [Delete history tips](http://www.clearallhistory.com/delete-history.html)  
\- [Clear Internet history](http://www.clearallhistory.com/clear-internet-history.html)  
\- [Proxy for YouTube](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-for-youtube.html)  
\- [Facebook proxy list](http://www.proxyway.com/www/proxy-facebook.html)  
\- [File wiper](http://www.mywiper.com/)  
\- [Bebo unblocker](http://www.proxyway.com/www/bebo-unblocker.html)  
\- [Free Bebo proxy](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-bebo-proxy.html)  
\- [YouTube bypass list](http://www.proxyway.com/www/youtube-bypass.html)  
\- [YouTube proxies](http://www.proxyway.com/www/youtube-proxies.html)  
\- [Clear recent documents list](http://www.proxyway.com/www/clear-recent-documents.html)  
\- [Proxy server software](http://www.proxyway.com/www/free-proxy-tool/anonymous-proxy-server-software.html)  
\- [Configure proxy settings](http://www.proxyway.com/www/set-proxy-configuration/configure-proxy-settings.html)  
\- [Anonymous browsing](http://www.proxyway.com/www/anonymous-browsing-features.html)  
\- [Anonymous internet surfing](http://www.proxyway.com/www/anonymous-internet-surfing.html)  
\- [Clear history](http://www.proxyway.com/www/clear-history-automatically.html)  
\- [Facebook proxy servers](http://www.proxyway.com/www/facebook-proxy-servers.html)  
\- [Cookies manager](http://www.proxyway.com/www/cookies-manager-stopper.html)  
\- [Ads blocker](http://www.proxyway.com/www/ads-blocker-stopper-ad.html)  
\- [Popup blocker](http://www.proxyway.com/www/popup-blocker-stopper.html)  
\- [Secret IP](http://www.secretip.com/)  
\- [Free Download Manager](http://www.freedownloadmanager.org/)  
\- [Nu Techno](http://www.nutechno.com/)  
\- [Clean cookies](http://www.proxyway.com/www/clean-cookies.html)  
\- [YouTube proxy sites](http://www.proxyway.com/www/youtube-proxy.html)  
\- [Facebook proxy sites](http://www.proxyway.com/www/facebook-proxy.html)  
\- [YouTube proxy for school](http://www.proxyway.com/www/youtube-proxy-for-school.html)  
\- [Facebook proxy list](http://www.proxyway.com/www/facebook-proxy-list.html)  
\- [Unblock Facebook](http://www.proxyway.com/www/unblock-facebook.html)  
\- [Site Frost](http://sitefrost.com/)  
\- [Remove history](http://www.proxyway.com/www/remove-history.html)  
\- [New YouTube proxy](http://www.proxyway.com/www/new-youtube-proxy.html)  
\- [Unblock YouTube at school](http://www.proxyway.com/www/unblock-youtube-at-school.html)  
\- [File Guru](http://www.fileguru.com/)  
\- [Proxy for YouTube](http://www.proxyway.com/www/unblock-youtube-proxy-site.html)  
\- [Bypass proxy sites](http://www.proxyway.com/www/bypass-proxy-sites.html)  
\- [Unlock Facebook tips](http://www.proxyway.com/www/unlock-facebook.html)  
\- [How to get on YouTube at school](http://www.proxyway.com/www/get-on-youtube-at-school.html) |   
---|---|---  
  
TIP OF THE DAY   
  
|  |  |   
---|---|---  
Copyright © 2010 [ProxyWay.com](http://www.proxyway.com/) All rights reserved. | [Terms of Use](http://www.proxyway.com/www/info/proxyway-terms.html) | [Privacy Policy](http://www.proxyway.com/www/info/proxyway-privacy.html) | [Check IP](http://www.proxyway.com/www/check-ip-address/whatis-my-ip-address.html) | [Site Map](http://www.proxyway.com/www/site_map.html) | [Useful Sites](http://www.proxyway.com/www/useful-sites.html)
